(Zack:)We're going
to be late.
(Sheldon:)I'm pacing nervously.
(Leonard:)You're jogging.
(Sheldon:)This is how the
Flash paces.
Just chill out, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)I'm not Sheldon.
I'm the Flash.
(Sheldon:)And now I'm going
to the Grand Canyon
(Sheldon:)to scream in frustration.
(Sheldon:)I'm back.
(Howard:)I'm Batman.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hardly think so.
(Sheldon:)The real caped crusader calls
his crime-fighting cohorts
(Sheldon:)when he's running late.
(Howard:)I had to walk.
(Howard:)I couldn't get Raj
on the back of my scooter.
(Raj:)I've said this before,
and I'll say it again.
(Raj:)Aquaman sucks.
(Zack:)Look up in the sky.
It's a bird. It's a plane.
(Zack:)I forget the rest.
(Penny:)All right. Let's get
this thing over with.